# MINA SAYED

A Mall Security Guard with five years of experience specializing in threat prevention, security, communication, and conflict resolution. A proven track record of identifying opportunities to improve security protocols and ensure safety of customers during high-pressure situations.

123 Carpenter Street, Philadelphia, PA, 12345 minasayed l@exa mple.com (123)456-7890

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **MALL SECURITY GUARD**

King of Prussia Mall, King of Prussia, PA Ju ne 2019- Present

- Provide security services for one of the largest malls in the United States with over 700+ daily customers per day, which included monitoring the premises for suspicious behavior and coordinating with a team of security guards to report incidents and irregularities
- Coordinate with fire departments and law enforcement agencies in response to emergency situations and security threats
- Identify conflict resolutions using de-escalation techniques to prevent violence and ensure the safety of customers

#### MALL SECURITY GUARD

Granite Run Mall, Lima, PA September 2017 - June2019

- Conducted patrols to detect security irregularities, breaches, and unusual behaviors to prevent theft and security breaches for retail stores in a mall with over 300+ patrons
- Responded to security alarms, detained individuals performing unlawful acts, and coordinated with police officers to report statements on security incidents during arrests

#### **EDUCATION**

High School Diploma

Benjamin Franklin High School, Philadelphia, PA September 2013- June 2017

### **KEY SKILLS**

- ♦ Security
- ♦ Threat Prevention
- ♦ Conflict Resolution
- ◆ Communication
- ♦ Safety Protocols

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Guard Card License #12345, State of Pennsylvania, 2017
- ◆ CPR Certified, Red Cross, 2017